// implementing  an array and passing the num, questions to quering, alternatives, and answers
let questions_Quering = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which bridge is known as 'bridge in the sky'?",
    answer: "Nine Arch Bridge",
    options: [
      "Palk Strait bridge",
      "Nine Arch Bridge",
      "Manampitiya Bridge",
      "Kinniya Bridge",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is an unrelated name for Kindom Kandy?",
    answer: "Pulathisipura",
    options: [
      "Kanda Uda Pasrata",
      "Senkadagala Kingdom",
      "Kandyan Kingdom",
      "Pulathisipura",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the oldest shrine in Kandy?",
    answer: "Natha Devalaya",
    options: [
      "Natha Devalaya",
      "The Temple of Tooth Relic",
      "Lankatilaka Temple",
      "Galamaduwa Raja Maha Viharaya",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who was the last king rules Kindom of Kandy?",
    answer: "King Sri Vikrama Rajasinha",
    options: [
      "King Sri vira parakrama Narendrasighe",
      "King Parakramabahu ",
      "King Sri Vikrama Rajasinha",
      "king Pandukabaya",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Which is the sneak peak of Sri Lanka's First Multi Religious Centre?",
    answer: "Ambuluwawa Tower",
    options: [
      "Ambuluwawa Tower",
      "Kokavil Tower",
      "Dawson Tower",
      "Lotus Tower",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which lake was called as 'The Sea of Milk'?",
    answer: "Kandy Lake",
    options: ["Gregory Lake", "Kandy Lake", "Kala Wewa", "Sembuwatta Lake"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who build Dalada Maligawa?",
    answer: "King Wimaladharmasuriya",
    options: [
      "King Devanampiyathissa",
      "King Buwanekabahu",
      "King Wimaladharmasuriya",
      "King Dutugamunu",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the largest botanical garden in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Peradeniya Botanical Garden",
    options: [
      "Peradeniya Botanical Garden",
      "Hakgala Botanical Garden",
      "Henarathgoda Botanical Garden",
      "Seethawaka Botanical Garden",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "what is the annual festival of tooth relic?",
    answer: "Esala Perahera Festival",
    options: [
      "Katina Perahera Festival",
      "Randoli Perahera Festival",
      "Vesak Perahera Festival",
      "Esala Perahera Festival",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of these is not a hill station?",
    answer: "Benthota",
    options: ["Nuwara Eliya", "Benthota", "Kandy", "Ella"],
  },
];
